Guide to the J. B. Matthews Papers, 1862-1986 and undated
J. B. Matthews papers 1862-1986 and undated
- Vertical Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s Part VI
  - Union Films, undated (Folder 10)
  - Union for Democratic Action, 1941-1947& undated (Folder 11-12)
  - Union for Democratic Socialism, 1956 (Folder 13)
  - Union for the Protection of the Human Person, 1959-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Union Label, 1946-1957& undated (Folder 15)
  - Union League Club, 1950 (Folder 16)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1960-1968 (Folder 17)
  - Union of California Veterans, 1950 (Folder 18)
  - Union of International Associations, 1958 (Folder 19)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1947-1970 (Folder 20)
  - Union of Soviet Societies for Friendship and Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, 1961-1962 (Folder 21)
  - Union of White Organizers, 1968 (Folder 22)
  - Union Security Committee, 1950 (Folder 23)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1950-1964 (Folder 24)
  - Unions and the Taft-Hartley Law, 1984& undated (Folder 25)
  - L'Unita de Popolo, 1945-1947 (Folder 26)
  - Unitarian Fellowship for Social Justice, 1956-1966 (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Unitarian Laymen's League, 1959 (Folder 2)
  - Unitarian Service Committee, Inc., 1950, 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Unitarian Universalist Association, 1961, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Unitarian Universalist Ministers for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 5)
  - The United Action Campaign Committee, undated (Folder 6)
  - United African Nationalist Movement, 1966 (Folder 7)
  - United Afro-American Association, 1967-1968 (Folder 8)
  - United Aid for Victims of Communism, Inc., undated (Folder 9)
  - United American Artists, 1939-1941& undated (Folder 10)
  - United American Spanish Aid Committee, 1940-1941& undated (Folder 11)
  - United Auto Workers, 1950-1970& undated (Folder 12)
  - United Beauty Culturalist Union, 1941 (Folder 13)
  - United Black Association, 1968 (Folder 14)
  - United Black Brotherhood, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - United Black Brothers, 1968-1969& undated (Folder 16)
  - United Black Hands, U.S.A., 1968 (Folder 17)
  - United Black Nationalists, 1967 (Folder 18)
  - United Black Students, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - United Blacks Against Genocide, 1967 (Folder 20)
  - United China Relief Inc., 1941 (Folder 21)
  - United Christian Citizens, 1952, 1955 (Folder 22)
  - United Christian Council for Democracy, 1947 (Folder 23)
  - United Church of Christ, 1944-1966& undated (Folder 24)
  - United Church Women, undated (Folder 25)
  - United Citizen's Review of Official Conduct, 1969 (Folder 26)
  - United Committee Against the War, 1966-1967 (Folder 27)
  - United Committee for a Progressive Union, 1942 (Folder 28)
  - United Committee for Democratic Rights, 1949 (Folder 29)
  - United Committee in Support of the Struggle Against Spanish Fascism, undated (Folder 30)
  - United Committee of Action, 1935 (Folder 31)
  - The United Committee of South-Slavic Americans, 1944-1945 (Folder 32)
  - United Committee to Commemorate the Tenth Anniversary of Warsaw Ghetto Uprising, 1953-1957 (Folder 33)
  - United Committee to Save the Jewish State and the United Nations, 1948 (Folder 34)
  - United Council of Working Class Women, undated (Folder 35)
  - United Croatians of America and Canada, undated (Folder 36)
  - United Czechoslovak-American Youth of Chicago, 1939 (Folder 37)
  - United Defense Committee Against Loyalty Checks, 1950 (Folder 38)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
    - General Papers, 1941-1954 (Box 531, Folder 1-6)
    - General Papers, 1955-1969& undated (Box 532, Folder 1-3)
    - Individuals, undated (Folder 4-5)
    - UE News, 1949-1956,June (Box 533, Folder 1-6)
    - UE News, 1956, July-1959, June (Box 534, Folder 1-6)
    - UE News, 1959, July-1962, June (Box 535, Folder 1-6)
    - UE News, 1962, July-1965 (Box 536, Folder 1-5)
  - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, 1967-1970 (Folder 6)
  - United Federal Workers of America, 1938-1941 (Folder 7)
  - United Financial Employees, undated (Folder 8)
  - United for Peace, 1967 (Folder 9)
  - United for Peace Party, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - United Front, undated (Folder 11)
  - United Front Against British and United States Imperialism, 1970 (Folder 12)
  - United Front Against Fascism, 1969 (Folder 13)
  - United Front for Herndon, 1935 (Folder 14)
  - United Front of Black People, 1968 (Folder 15)
  - United Front Organizations, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - United Fruit Company, 1954& undated (Box 537, Folder 1)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, 1945-1952 (Folder 2)
  - United Harlem Tenants and Consumers Organization, 1946 (Folder 3)
  - United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers, undated (Folder 4)
  - United Independent Socialist Committee, 1958-1959 (Folder 5)
  - United Independent-Socialist Electoral Ticket, 1958 (Folder 6)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1942 (Folder 7)
  - United Jewish Youth, 1941& undated (Folder 8)
  - United Labor Action Committee, 1951-1952& undated (Folder 9)
  - United Labor and Citizens Committee for Jobs and Recovery, undated (Folder 10)
  - United Labor and People's Committee for May day, 1949-1953& undated (Folder 11)
  - United Labor Committee to Defeat Taft-Hartley, 1950& undated (Folder 12)
  - United Labor Committee to Free the 12 Communist and to Defend Constitutional Liberties, 1949 (Folder 13)
  - United Labor Committee to Repeal the Taft-Hartley Law, 1949& undated (Folder 14)
  - United Labor May Day Committee, 1939& undated (Folder 15)
  - United Liberals and Socialist, 1958-1959 (Folder 16)
  - United Lubliner Relief, undated (Folder 17)
  - United May Day Committee - Papers, 1924-1969& undated (Folder 18-19)
  - United Nations
    - General Papers, 1943-1953,Nov. (Box 538, Folder 1-5)
    - General Papers, 1953, Dec.-1959 (Box 539, Folder 1-5)
    - General Papers, 1960-1972& undated (Box 540, Folder 1-4)
    - American Association for the United Nations, 1945-1968& undated (Folder 1-5)
    - UNESCO
      - General Papers, 1945-1956 (Box 541, Folder 1-6)
      - General Papers, 1957-1969& undated (Box 542, Folder 1-5)
      - The UNESCO Courier, 1955, Jan.-Apr. (Folder 6)
      - Towards World Understanding, Nos. 1, 3-6, 8-11 (Folder 7)
    - UNICEF, 1956-1970& undated (Box 543, Folder 1-2)
    - World Health Organization, 1948-1958& undated (Folder 3)
    - World Youth Assembly, 1970 (Folder 4)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1966-1969& undated (Folder 5)
  - United Nations Law Reports, 1966-1967- Issued by Walker and Company (Folder 6)
  - United Nations News, 1947& undated (Folder 7)
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1948 (Folder 8)
  - United Nations-United States, 1945-1954 (Folder 9)
  - United Nations World, 1947-1952& undated (Folder 10)
  - United Negro and Allied Veterans of America, 1947 (Box 544, Folder 1)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1938-1950& undated (Folder 2)
  - United Optical Workers of America, 1947 (Folder 3)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1947-1961 (Folder 4)
  - United Palestine Appeal, 1948 (Folder 5)
  - United Parents Association of N.Y.C., 1946, 1956 (Folder 6)
  - United Philadelphia Vets for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 7)
  - United Popular Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1949 (Folder 8)
  - United Presbyterian Church, U.S.A.
    - Papers, 1951-1958 (Folder 9-13)
    - Papers, 1959-1969& undated (Box 545, Folder 1-3)
  - United Public Workers of America, 1946-1967& undated (Folder 4-5)
  - United Railway Workers of America, undated (Folder 6)
  - United Rank and File Committee, undated (Folder 7)
  - United Rank and File Educational Committee, 1948& undated (Folder 8)
  - United Resistance Fund, 1967 (Folder 9)
  - United Revisionists, 1963, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - United Rubber Workers, 1966-1967 (Folder 11)
  - United Secularists of America, 1956 (Box 546, Folder 1)
  - United Service for New Americans Chapter, undated (Folder 2)
  - United Service to China, Inc., 1948-1949 (Folder 3)
  - United Servicemen's Fund, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - United Shoe Workers of America, 1947-1952& undated (Folder 5)
  - United Socialist Alliance, U.S.A., 1956-1957 (Folder 6)
  - The United Socialist Political Action Committee, 1958 (Folder 7)
  - United States Advisory Commission on Information, 1949 (Folder 8)
  - United States Arrangements Committee for the World Youth Conference, 1945-1946& undated (Folder 9)
  - United States. Coast Guard: Waterfront Exclusion List, 1956 (Folder 10)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights, 1966 (Folder 11)
  - United States Committee for Refugees, 1968-1969 (Folder 12)
  - United States Committee for the Christian Peace Conference, 1966-1967 (Folder 13)
  - United States Committee for the United Nations, 1957-1960 (Folder 14)
  - United States Congress Against War, 1933 (Folder 15)
  - United States Constitution Council, 1968 (Folder 16)
  - United States Day Committee, Inc., 1955 (Folder 17)
  - United States. Department of Agriculture, 1946 (Folder 18)
  - United States. Department of Labor, 1968-1969 (Folder 19)
  - United States Festival Committee, 1953 (Folder 20)
  - United States Independent Telephone Association, 1974 (Folder 21)
  - United States National Student Association, 1948-1967 (Folder 22)
  - United States. Office of Education, 1966 (Folder 23)
  - United States Olympic Association and United States Olympic Committee, 1959 (Folder 24)
  - United States. Post Office Department, 1959-1965 (Folder 25)
  - United States Servicemen's Fund, 1970 (Box 547, Folder 1)
  - United States Sponsoring Committee of the Inter-Continental Peace Conference, 1952 (Folder 2)
  - United States Student Assembly, 1945 (Folder 3)
  - United Steel Workers of America, 1966-1967 (Folder 4)
  - United Summer Appeal for Children, 1953 (Folder 5)
  - United Wholesale Warehouse Workers Union, 1946 (Folder 6)
  - United World Federalists, Inc., 1950-1969& undated (Folder 7-10)
  - United Youth Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy, undated (Folder 11)
  - United Yugoslav Relief Fund of America, 1946 (Folder 12)
  - United Zionists-Revisionists of America, 1933 (Folder 13)
  - Unity, 1957-1958 (Folder 14)
  - Universal Distributors Company, 1949-1951 (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - The Universal Viewpoint, 1958 (Folder 2)
  - Universities Committee Against the ABM, 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace, 1963-1965 (Folder 4)
  - Universities General, 1965, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Universities National Anti-War Fund, 1970 (Folder 6)
  - The University and Science for Peace and Social Progress, 1972 (Folder 7)
  - The University Bookman, 1967-1974 (Folder 8)
  - University Center For Rational Alternatives, 1970 (Folder 9)
  - University Christian Foundation, 1967-1969 (Folder 10)
  - University Christian Movement, 1968-1969 (Folder 11)
  - University Circle Teach-in Committee, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - University Committee on the Dominican Republic, 1965 (Folder 13)
  - University Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 14)
  - University Committee to Protest the War in Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 15)
  - University Federation for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1938 (Folder 16)
  - University of Arizona, 1969 (Folder 17)
  - University of Buffalo, 1964, 1971 (Folder 18)
  - University of California, 1950-1969& undated (Folder 19)
  - University of California-Berkeley
    - Papers, 1960-1966 (Folder 20-21)
    - Papers, 1967-1969& undated (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - University of California-Los Angeles, 1950-1970 (Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago, 1949-1969 (Folder 3)
  - University of Colorado, 1950-1969 (Folder 4)
  - University of Connecticut, 1969 (Folder 5)
  - University of Dayton, 1967 (Folder 6)
  - University of Denver, 1969 (Folder 7)
  - University of Hawaii, 1965-1969 (Folder 8)
  - University of Illinois, 1949-1968& undated (Folder 9)
  - University of Illinois Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1968-1969 (Folder 10)
  - University of Kansas, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - University of Massachusetts, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - University of Michigan, 1966-1967& undated (Folder 13)
  - University of Minnesota, 1960-1969 (Folder 14)
  - University of New Hampshire, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1948-1970& undated (Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1957 (Folder 18)
  - University of Rochester, 1967 (Folder 19)
  - University of South Florida, undated (Folder 20)
  - University of Texas, 1967, 1969 (Folder 21)
  - University of Washington
    - Papers, 1948-1969& undated (Box 550, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1949 (Folder 2)
  - University of Washington Vietnam Committee, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - University Place Bookshop, 1950-1968& undated (Folder 4)
  - University Socialist Committee, 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1952-1953& undated (Folder 6)
  - Up Against the Wall, 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Up From Under, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Up Front, 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Uphaus, Williard, 1957, 1961 (Folder 10)
  - Uptight, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Upward Bound, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Urban Reports Corporation, 1969-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Urey, Harold C., 1949& undated (Folder 14)
  - US, 1967-1969 (Folder 15)
  - The Utica Peace Center, 1968 (Folder 16)
  - Utility Workers Union of America, 1948 (Folder 17)
  - V.J. Jerome Memorial Publications Committee, 1966 (Box 551, Folder 1)
  - V.O.I.C.E., 1972-1974 (Folder 2)
  - Victor Gollanoz, Ltd., 1944 (Folder 3)
  - Victory Committee of German-American Trade Unionists, 1942 (Folder 4)
  - Victory Council of the Foreign Language Press of New York, 1943 (Folder 5)
  - Viet-Report, 1965-1967 (Folder 6-7)
  - Vietnam
    - Papers, 1964-1971 (Folder 8-10)
    - Papers, 1972-1973& undated (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam Coalition: Americans for De-escalation Candidates, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Courier, 1969-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Vietnam Curriculum, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Day Committee, 1965-1969& undated (Folder 5-9)
  - Vietnam Dollar Fund, 1966 (Box 553, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam Draft Hearings Committee, 1967 (Folder 2)
  - Vietnam GI, 1968-1969 (Folder 3)
  - Vietnam Gift Pac. 1970 (Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Information Group, 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Inquiry, 1967 (Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Moratorium Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 7-10)
  - Vietnam Newsletter, 1966 (Folder 11)
  - Vietnam Peace Parade, 1968-1970 (Folder 12)
  - Vietnam Summer, 1967 (Folder 13-14)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, 1967-1970 (Box 554, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam Work-in, 1967-1968 (Folder 2)
  - Viewpoint Books, undated (Folder 3)
  - Vigilance Incorporated, 1951 (Folder 4)
  - Village Conference for Legislative Action, undated (Folder 5)
  - The Village Voice, 1958 (Folder 6)
  - Villagers Opposed to the War, 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Vilnis, 1944 (Folder 8)
  - Vincent, J.T., 1950 (Folder 9)
  - Violence, 1970 (Folder 9a)
  - Virginia Citizens for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - The Virginia Committee to Impeach Governor Almond, 1959 (Folder 11)
  - The Virginia Weekly, 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Visscher, Maurice, 1942-1948 (Folder 13)
  - The Vito Marcantonio Memorial, 1955-1957 (Folder 14)
  - Vocations for Social Change, Inc., 1968-1969 (Folder 15)
  - Vogeler, Robert A., 1950-1952 (Folder 16)
  - The Voice for Human Rights, 1939 (Folder 17)
  - Voice for Survival, 1968 (Folder 18)
  - Voice of Action, 1934(Seattle, WA) (Folder 19)
  - Voice of America
    - Papers, 1950& undated (Folder 20)
    - Hearings Before the Committee on Government Operations, 1953 (Folder 21-23)
  - Voice of Freedom Committee, 1947-1953& undated (Box 555, Folder 1)
  - Voice of the People Against Federal Aid to Education, 1957 (Folder 2)
  - Voice of Women, 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Voice of Youth, 1935 (Folder 4)
  - Voice Party, 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Volunteers in Service to America, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Voorhis, Jerry, 1961 (Folder 7)
  - Voters Alliance for Americans of German Ancestry, 1953 (Folder 8)
  - Voters Committee for Peace, 1967 (Folder 9)
  - Voters for Peace, 1962-1967 (Folder 10)
  - W.P.A. Teachers' Union, 1939-1940& undated (Folder 11)
  - Wackenhut Corporation, 1966-1971 (Folder 12)
  - The Wade Defense Committee, 1956-1957 (Folder 13)
  - Wadleigh, Henry Julian, 1949 (Folder 14)
  - Wage Earners Committee, 1952 (Folder 15)
  - Wagner, Walter, 1955 (Folder 16)
  - Walk for Peace Committee, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Walker, Edwin, 1972 (Folder 18)
  - Walker-Lassiter Defense Fund, 1959-1960 (Folder 19)
  - Walker, Margaret, 1965 (Folder 20)
  - Wallace Brown, Inc., 1957-1958 (Folder 21)
  - Wallace, George, 1968-1973 (Box 556, Folder 1)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1952-1956 (Folder 2)
  - Wallace Campaign, 1945-1949 (Folder 3-4)
  - Wallace for President Committee, 1948 (Folder 5)
  - Wallkins, Phil, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Walls, W.J., 1957 (Folder 7)
  - Walsh, Raymond, 1955 (Folder 8)
  - Walt Whitman School of Social Sciences, 1946-1947 (Folder 9)
  - Waltor Committee Hearings, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - War Activities Committee-Motion Picture Industry, 1942-1945 (Folder 11)
  - War Bond Committee, 1966 (Folder 12)
  - War Control Planners, Inc., 1969 (Folder 13)
  - The War Corporation, 1966 (Folder 14)
  - War Department, 1946 (Folder 15)
  - War/Peace Report, 1961-1971 (Folder 16)
  - War Resisters League
    - Papers, 1933-1966 (Box 557, Folder 1-5)
    - Papers, 1967-1973& undated (Box 558, Folder 1-4)
  - War Tax Resistance, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - War Veterans' Peace Association, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Warbasse, James, undated (Folder 7)
  - Warburg, James, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Ward, George, 1950 (Folder 9)
  - Ward, Harry F., 1939, 1963 (Folder 10)
  - Ward, Lynd, 1955 (Folder 11)
  - Warren, Charles, 1963 (Folder 12)
  - Wartime Budget Conference, 1944(for NYC) (Folder 13)
  - Washington, Bertram Alexander, 1949-1950 (Folder 14)
  - Washington Action Project, 1965 (Folder 15)
  - Washington Ad Hoc Committee for August 6 Protest Against the War in Vietnam, 1966 (Folder 16)
  - Washington Anti-Hearst Committee, 1936 (Folder 17)
  - Washington Area Citizens Against the ABM, 1969 (Folder 18)
  - Washington Area Citizens Forum, 1956-1961 (Folder 19)
  - Washington Area Committee for the Abolition of the House Un-American Activities Committee, 1961-1968 (Box 559, Folder 1)
  - Washington Area Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Folder 2)
  - Washington Baptist Convention, 1960 (Folder 3)
  - Washington Bookshop, 1941& undated (Folder 4)
  - Washington CIO Committee to Reinstate Helen Miller, 1941 (Folder 5)
  - Washington Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Washington Committee for Academic Freedom, 1948& undated (Folder 7)
  - Washington Committee for Aid to China, 1939-1941 (Folder 8)
  - Washington Committee for Democratic Action, 1940& undated (Folder 9)
  - Washington Committee for Democratic Rights, 1940 (Folder 10)
  - Washington Committee for Non-Participation in Japanese Aggression, 1940-1941 (Folder 11)
  - Washington Committee for Spanish Refugee Aid, 1940 (Folder 12)
  - Washington Committee for the Abolition of the HUAC, 1961 (Folder 13)
  - Washington Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee (Washington State), 1967 (Folder 14)
  - Washington Committee to Aid Agricultural Workers, 1939-1941 (Folder 15)
  - Washington Committee to Aid China, 1938-1941& undated (Folder 16)
  - Washington Committee to Celebrate the 300th Year of Jewish Settlement in the U.S., 1935 (Folder 17)
  - Washington Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights, 1951-1952 (Folder 18)
  - Washington Committee to Lift the Spanish Embargo, 1939 (Folder 19)
  - Washington Committee to Revise the Neutrality Act, 1939 (Folder 20)
  - Washington Conference on Peaceful Alternative to the Atlantic Pact, 1949& undated (Folder 21)
  - Washington Cooperative Bookshop Association, 1941-1957& undated (Folder 22)
  - Washington Cultural Co-op, 1960 (Folder 23)
  - Washington Cultural Society, undated (Folder 24)
  - Washington Draft Resistance Union, 1968 (Folder 25)
  - Washington Ethical Society, 1965 (Folder 26)
  - Washington Fellowship House, 1961 (Folder 27)
  - Washington Free Press, 1967-1969 (Folder 28)
  - Washington Freedom of the Press Committee, 1957-1958 (Folder 29)
  - Washington Friends Joint Peace Committee, 1957 (Folder 30)
  - Washington Friends of Spanish Democracy, 1938& undated (Folder 31)
  - Washington Heights Committee to End the War in Vietnam Now, 1966 (Folder 32)
  - Washington Jewish Children's School, 1955 (Folder 33)
  - Washington Labor Peace Committee, 1938 (Folder 34)
  - Washington League of Women Shoppers, undated (Folder 35)
  - Washington Legislative News, 1940 (Folder 36)
  - Washington Mobilization Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 560, Folder 1)
  - Washington Mobilization for Peace, 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Washington Observer, 1967-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Washington Pacifist Fellowship, 1961-1962 (Folder 4)
  - Washington Peace Center, 1964-1968 (Folder 5)
  - Washington Peace Mobilization, 1940 (Folder 6)
  - Washington Pension Union, 1953-1939& undated (Folder 7)
  - Washington Political Cabaret, 1939 (Folder 8)
  - The Washington Post, 1950-1969 (Folder 9)
  - Washington Professors for World Peace, 1964 (Folder 10)
  - The Washington Religious Review, 1957 (Folder 11)
  - Washington State Civil Congress, 1949 (Folder 12)
  - Washington Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1968 (Folder 13)
  - Washington Tom Mooney Committee, 1939 (Folder 14)
  - Washington Training Conference for American Delegation to the World Youth Conference, undated (Folder 15)
  - Washington War Tax Resistance, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Washington Youth Council, 1940& undated (Folder 17)
  - Washington Young Friends (Quakers), 1960 (Folder 18)
  - The Washington's Birthday Defense Committee, 1971 (Folder 19)
  - The Watchman Examiner, 1953-1957 (Folder 20)
  - Waterbury Peace Committee, 1967 (Folder 21)
  - Watkins Committee, 1954 (Folder 22)
  - Watson, Goodwin, 1941& undated (Folder 23-24)
  - Watumull Foundation, 1947-1948 (Folder 25)
  - Wayne Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 26)
  - We Dissent, 1960 (Box 561, Folder 1)
  - We Go For Joe Group, 1954 (Folder 2)
  - We Shall Overcome, 1965 (Folder 3)
  - We, The People, 1957, 1971 (Folder 4)
  - We Will Bury You, 1962 (Folder 5)
  - Weapon, 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Weathermen, 1970 (Folder 7)
  - The Weavers, 1952-1963 (Folder 8)
  - Webster, Margaret, 1942-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Wechsler, Maurice, 1948-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Wechsler, Nancy, 1959 (Folder 11)
  - Weekly Crusader, 1964-1968 (Folder 12)
  - Weekly Guardian Associates, Inc., 1956 (Folder 13)
  - Weekly People, 1945 (Folder 14)
  - Weinbaum, Sidney, 1950 (Folder 15)
  - Weinberg, Joseph W., 1949-1953 (Folder 16)
  - Weizmann Histadrut Club, undated (Folder 17)
  - Welfare Rights Committee, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Welfare Workers for Peace in Vietnam, 1965-1967& undated (Folder 19)
  - Weller, Charles, undated (Folder 20)
  - Welles, Orson, 1938-1943 (Folder 21)
  - Wells Defense Committee, 1953 (Folder 22)
  - Weltfish, Gene, 1955 (Folder 23)
  - Wendell Phillips Academic Freedom Committee, 1961-1962 (Folder 24)
  - Wennerstrom, Stig, 1963 (Folder 25-26)
  - Wentzel, Fred, 1955 (Folder 27)
  - Wesleyan University, 1968 (Folder 28)
  - West Coast Vacation School, 1963 (Box 562, Folder 1)
  - West Contra Costa Peace Center, 1967 (Folder 2)
  - West, Donald, 1957 (Folder 3)
  - West End Black Turks, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - West End Community Council, 1968 (Folder 5)
  - West Indies National Emergency Committee, 1940 (Folder 6)
  - West Side Actors Workshop and Repertory, 1966 (Folder 7)
  - West Side Committee for Friendly Relations with Cuba, 1961 (Folder 8)
  - West Side Committee on Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 9)
  - West Side Committee to Bring the Troops Home Now, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - West Side Committee to Defend the Panthers, 1970 (Folder 11)
  - West Side Council on Religious and Civic Organizations, 1945 (Folder 12)